David Thompson: Welcome to the engineering standup. Let's do a quick round of updates.
Emma Wilson: I'll go first. I completed the API integration yesterday. Running final tests today.
David Thompson: Excellent. Any blockers?
Emma Wilson: No blockers, but I need to update the documentation. Will do that this afternoon.
James Lee: For my update, I'm still working on the database migration. Should be done by tomorrow.
David Thompson: James, do you need any help with that?
James Lee: I think I'm good, but I'll let you know if I run into issues. I'll also need to create a rollback plan.
David Thompson: Good thinking. Make sure to document the rollback procedure.
Emma Wilson: I can review the migration script if you want a second pair of eyes.
James Lee: That would be great, Emma. I'll send it to you later today.
David Thompson: Perfect. I'll handle the deployment coordination with DevOps.
David Thompson: Also, we need to schedule the security audit. I'll reach out to the security team today.
Emma Wilson: Should we include the new API endpoints in that audit?
David Thompson: Absolutely. Good catch. I'll make sure they're included.
James Lee: I'll also prepare the performance benchmarks before the deployment.
David Thompson: Great. Let's recap the action items:
David Thompson: Emma will update API documentation and review James's migration script.
David Thompson: James will complete the database migration and create a rollback plan.
David Thompson: I'll coordinate with DevOps and schedule the security audit.
David Thompson: James will also prepare performance benchmarks.
Emma Wilson: Sounds good. Same time tomorrow?
David Thompson: Yes, let's keep the daily standups going this week.
James Lee: Works for me. See you all tomorrow.
David Thompson: Thanks everyone. Have a productive day!